Guide to the Duke University Press Records, 1812-1991
Duke University. University Archives
- Carlyle Letters, 1812-1856, (11 boxes)
  This series contains facisimiles of the Thomas and Jane Welsh Carlyle letters which comprise The Collected Letters of Thomas and Jane Welsh Carlyle, published by the Duke University Press. The facsimilies are arranged chronologically. Also included are chronology cards.
  - Chronology Cards (Box 12)
  - Facsimiles, 1812-1826 (Box 13)
  - Facsimiles, 1827-1835 (Box 14)
  - Facsimiles, 1836-1841 (Box 15)
  - Facsimiles, 1842-1844 July (Box 16)
  - 1844 Aug.-1847 (Box 17)
  - 1848-1850 (Box 18)
  - 1850-1851 (Box 19)
  - 1852-1853 June (Box 20)
  - 1853 July-1855 June (Box 21)
  - 1855 July-1856 Oct. (Box 22)